mybigcommerce.com 2015-12-10

# Privacy Policy | Bigcommerce

## Privacy policy.

Last updated: March 20, 2014

This is the website of **Bigcommerce**.

Our postal address is:  
Level 6, 1-3 Smail St  
Ultimo NSW 2007  
Australia

We can be reached via email at [sales@bigcommerce.co](mailto:mailto:sales@bigcommerce.co)m or you can reach us by telephone at (US) 1-888-699-8911 or (Int) +1-512-758-7588.

We take your privacy seriously. Because we gather certain types of information about our users, we want to help you understand the terms and conditions surrounding the collection and use of that information. This privacy statement discloses the types of information we gather, how we use it, and how to correct or change it. These privacy practices apply to the website located at the [www.bigcommerce.com](https://www.bigcommerce.com/) and related Bigcommerce websites, pages, applications, and mobile applications (collectively, the "Site"), that you were viewing when you clicked through to this policy, which is operated directly by us or by our affiliated companies.

For each visitor to our Site, our web server automatically recognizes no information regarding the domain or email address except for information gathered utilizing Google Analytics. We collect the email addresses of those who communicate with us via email. These email addresses are used for internal review only. We use cookies to allow Bigcommerce customers to log in to their account.

If you do not want to receive email from us in the future, please let us know by sending us email at the above address.

When you interact with our Site, for example by making a purchase or subscribing to an email list, we may collect information about you including but not limited to your name, address, telephone number, and email address.

We may share this information with our affiliated companies who are controlled by, who control or who are under common control with Bigcommerce.

We may share this information along with a record of any transactions you conduct on our Site or offline with us with a third-party advertising partner and its service providers in order to deliver you advertising tailored to your interests when you visit certain other websites. Data shared with our third-party partner is made anonymous.

We may use third parties to help us provide services and marketing to you, such as processing payments, fulfilling orders or designing website templates for your use. If personally identifiable information is provided to any of these third parties, we will require that such information be maintained by them in strictest confidence.

We use cookies to allow Bigcommerce customers to login to their account. We may use technologies such as our own cookies to provide you with enhanced online display advertising tailored to your interests. To opt out of advertising provided by us, click here.

We may participate in behavioral-based advertising. This means that a third party may place a cookie on your browser, or use a web beacon, to collect information about your use of our website so that they can provide advertising about products and services tailored to your interest. That advertising may appear either on our website, or on other websites. If you would like to opt-out from having the behavioral-based advertising companies with whom we have a relationship use your information for advertising purposes you can do so by visiting the [Network Advertising Initiative](https://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/) or [Digital Advertising Alliance](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/). Opting out will not in any way affect your use of our Site.

We may participate in demographic, interest, and location based advertising. If we do so, we will not use personally identifiable information (PII) in conjunction with this information. You may opt out or customize your demographic and interest based settings, on the Google Display Network, using [Ad Settings](https://www.google.com/settings/ads).

At times, you may be directed to third party websites and/or offered the option to download an application using a third party platform. Our provision of a link to any other website or our provision of an application using a third party platform is for your convenience and does not signify our endorsement of such other website, platform or its contents. When you click on such a link or download and use such an application, you will leave our Site and go to another website. During this process, a third party may collect personally identifiable information from you. We have no control over, do not review, and cannot be responsible for, these outside websites or their content. Please be aware that the terms of this privacy policy do not apply to these outside websites or content, or to any collection of data after you click on a link to a third party. You will need to contact them to understand their privacy policies.

We are always seeking to improve our business. In accomplishing these objectives, we may buy or sell a company, or one or more of the companies in our corporate family may merge with or be acquired by another company. If we sell a business, we may transfer some or all of your information as a part of the sale in order that the service being provided to you may continue or for other business purposes.

Our Site is not directed to individuals under the age of thirteen (13), and we request that these individuals do not provide personal information through our Site. We do not knowingly collect information from children under thirteen (13) without parental consent. Visit the Federal Trade Commission website for more information about the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA).

This privacy policy is subject to change. Please review it periodically. If we make changes to the policy, we will revise the "Last Updated" date at the top of this policy. Any changes to this policy will become effective when we post the revised policy on the Site. Your use of the Site following these changes means that you accept the revised policy.

Upon request, we provide Site visitors with access to all information (including proprietary information) that we maintain about them.

We have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our Site.

If you feel that this Site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us at the above addresses or phone numbers.

IF YOU, FOR YOURSELF OR ON BEHALF OF ONE OR MORE PERSONS YOU ARE REPRESENTING WITH RESPECT TO BIGCOMMERCE SERVICES, DO NOT AGREE TO ANY OF THE FOREGOING TERMS, YOU MUST, FOR YOURSELF AND ON BEHALF ANY SUCH PERSON(S), DISCONTINUE THE REGISTRATION PROCESS, DISCONTINUE YOUR USE OF THE SERVICES, AND, IF YOU ARE ALREADY A MEMBER, CANCEL YOUR ACCOUNT. BEGINNING NOW, ANY CONTINUATION BY YOU IN USING THE SERVICES CONSTITUTES FOR YOU AND THOSE REPRESENTED BY YOU AN EXPRESS AFFIRMATION AND COMMITMENT TO BE (OR TO CONTINUE TO BE, AS APPLICABLE) LEGALLY BOUND BY AND TO COMPLY WITH ALL OF THESE TERMS.
